What's wrong? You didn't have dinner.
What is it?
Are you...
I hope you are not.
No, I'm not.
I don't want you to have a
baby before you get married.
I said I'm not.
We can't even cancel the marriage now.
You're thinking too far ahead again.
I wish I'm thinking ahead now.
Your period date is 11/12.
17 days has been passed since the date.
I'm a loser who can't even
protect a woman.
Maybe this is a good thing.
I feel inferior to you too.
I've wanted to break up
with you 12 times in a day.
I can't even make 50K in a year.
A marriage was too much for me.
Jung Hoon loves Hae Yoon.
I'm back.
You told Jung Hoon you're
leaving before you left?
Do you like him better than me?
Is he more trustworthy than I am?
I'm sorry. I was too busy.
You like Jung Hoon better. That's why you
called Jung Hoon even if you were too busy.
I didn't tell you because I knew
you'd question me like this.
- Did somebody come?
- I ordered food. I think it's here.
- Stop eating. You'll get fat eventually.
- Did something happen to you?
You're so cranky. I guess something
must've happened to you.
I guess you are my friend.
I'm having such hard times.
Talk to me later.
I need to eat now.
My situation is more
important than your hunger.
What are you doing here?
I need a dog tonight.
Come in.
Oh my god!
- Give me the blanket.
- Hae Yoon.
Where are you going?
Hey.
What's wrong with her?
Why am I naked?
We broke up anyway. I don't
care who he's dating.
You can't just leave like this.
Then should I dance?
You're so gross. You're
such a third-class person.
It hurts. Nothing happened between us.
She's just my best friend.
You saw me and her together before.
This wasn't the first time! When was it?
Since when did you guys do that?
I'm not that kind of person.
It's nothing.
What happened was...
she just became my dog.
And I became her dog.
A human became a dog. Do you
think this is nothing?
I saw it in a movie. Inuit hugs his dog
while sleeping when he feels cold.
I needed a dog to hug because you broke
up with me. I felt so cold and lonely.
Why did you break up with me?
- I watched that movie.
- You did? Then you should know.
That's why I cannot understand you.
In that movie, the two main
characters sleep together.
Not just sleeping, they love each other.
I didn't know.
This is good. I was worried how
I should forget about you.
Now everything is really over.
What are you doing? You
should've talked to her.
Don't you know Hae Yoon?
If she's really angry, we should leave
her alone until she calms down.
- I can talk to her after.
- Why was I naked?
- Do you really not remember anything?
- No, I don't.
- Never mind then.
- You look like something did happen.
What makes you so sure that
nothing happened between us?
What could happen between us? If it
could, it'd be killing each other.
- What's the title of the movie?
- What movie?
The movie about hugging the dog.
Park Joong Hoon and Jung
Yu Mi are in that movie?
Yeah.
Hey!
Do they have sex in the movie?
- Do they love each other?
- Yeah.
I didn't know that. You're not my friend.
I shouldn't have copied what you said.
You're responsible for this.
You said you guys broke up.
Why do you do that?
I want her to think I
was a good boyfriend.
I don't want her to remember
me as a third class person.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
You guys are best friends.
My situation is complicated enough already.
I'm going to open my business next weekend.
A business? In this situation?
My business homepage. I've
been working on this.
I'm going to announce the winner
of the wedding event by this week.
And I'm going to make the most beautiful
wedding and upload the video on YouTube.
You're stronger than I thought. I thought you
wouldn't do anything but cry for a while.
In terms of business, it's in my father's
genes to be very cold hearted.
You're talking as if you're a
daughter of a rich family.
Do they have to write, 'I'm from a rich
family' on their face to make it noticeable?
- You never know.
- I know you're not.
- There's not that much to fix.
- There is a lot.
This isn't my style.
Do whatever you want. I'll pay.
I like that attitude. I'll do whatever I want
because this is where I'm going to live.
- It's we, not just you.
- Yeah. It's a place where we live.
I guess for you, a marriage
is about you, not us.
I don't have any romance about marriage.
We all live by ourselves eventually.
Why are you being so nice today?
You're even listening to me.
Don't I always listen to you?
I thought you do when you want to.
Why aren't you saying no this time?
Because if I do, you might
call off the marriage.
You're playing hard to get.
I want to know the reason for that.
- Are you saying you like me?
- Didn't you know that?
I love every women.
I am not that picky about women.
But since you decided not to do it until
we actually get married, I'll stop here.
Mr. Min wants to come to Seoul just
to meet me? That's unexpected!
I'd love to do that. I can take
that as a good sign, right?
Okay.
Good job, Gong Ki Joong.
If I can make this work, I can negotiate with my dad when I ask him to invest.
Long time no see. I'm surea
the engagement went well.
Why am I asking this to you?
I'm such a loser.
You haven't changed. Hae Yoon
was so worried about you.
- When did you come back?
- Didn't you call me because you knew?
How did you know I came back?
I think I should hang up now.
I'm going to hang up first.
She sounds alright.
You look so happy. Is it
because of your marital home?
Don't just pump it. I got a
good sign from my investor.
I thought your dad is doing it.
That's that. There's something
I'm working on separately.
I'm going to show him that I'm doing
business by only getting help from him.
- Where's Min Ho?
- He's crazy about a woman.
He's out of his mind.
He must be getting old.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
What a beautiful sky.
Isn't this so romantic?
It's so cold!
It's freezing.
You have no emotion!
This is so good. I missed
your coffee with Min Ho.
So there is a love
at Min Ho's age too.
He's just unlucky because he
mistook his hormones for love.
I agree. I think it's a blessing to get
married with someone I don't love.
I don't think the woman thinks the same.
- Chae Young doesn't like me either.
- There's a woman who doesn't like you?
There is. It felt kind of weird but now
I'm glad that she doesn't like me.
What if she says she loves me? Then I
have to live like my parents forever.
I told myself I wouldn't live
like my parents. But I do live like them now.
I didn't understand my dad but
now I'm starting to.
I even respect him.
This is how a man is getting old.
Hello.
- The date for family fact-finding is set.
- When is it?
It's next Wednesday at 10 o'clock.
I have an important surgery next Wednesday.
Can you reschedule it to Thursday?
Yes, I can. I'll talk to the officer.
You're coming with me, right?
No, only you and your wife.
You need to know something before
you go, so stop by my office.
Okay.
Now it's starting.
The war of divorce.
- You wrote a marriage contract with her, right?
- Of course.
Without that, this marriage is meaningless.
The problem is a lawyer can't attend.
A family fact-finding officer will
ask you a question face to face
and write a report based on that. That
report is very important for the trial.
Another important thing is the officer's
view on you will be used for the trial.
What he thinks of you and your situation
can change the direction of this trial.
- You have to win his favor.
- How?
How could you make that decision
without discussing with me?
Leaving the house was that wrong?
Think about it. The officer is going to write his opinion on the report.
What does me leaving the house
have to do with the child?
Would the child be more comfortable living
where he is now, or in a familiar environment?
Is it better for him to live in the house that he's been in, or in a strange environment?
Go back to the house. Why do you have to leave the house?
You have to make your wife leave.
Then she's going to go to her mother's house.
That's good. Kids these days are very smart.
You said her family is kind of poor.
Do you think he feels comfortable
living there or his house?
Your kid would whine about that.
But what if my kid had bad influences?
Then give up the custody and parental right.
You know the saying, 'winner takes all' right?
We can have everything if we win.
We have to defend the affair
no matter what it takes.
Do you have this many expensive bags?
Is this a lot?
A family fact-finding officer is a public official.
You know how much they get paid?
To him, it is considered overspending
if you have this many bags.
Then how am I supposed
to answer that question?
Tell him you had to raise the cultural standard for your husband.
Tell him that you're close with this model
but it's not like what your wife thinks.
And tell him you did sleep with her a couple times.
He won't believe you if you say you didn't sleep with her at all.
Really?
It doesn't make sense not to sleep with a woman like her.
So you want to do it here. On the stairs?
Yeah.
- Is that what you want to do?
- Yeah.
How did those people think
the same thing as you did?
It's a kiss scene that was on a drama.
Most women have their kiss here.
I wanted you to do what you
want to do, not copying others.
Who cares?
Emulation is the mother of creation.
No.
I won't do it.
- Let's do it.
- No.
- I said no.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Now you can kiss me.
- Is that in a drama?
- Yeah.
- No.
- Yes, it was.
No. I think I saw that in a movie.
- I can't remember the title.
- Are you going to do it or not?
What was the name of the movie?
I forgot.
- What was it?
- I don't know!
I saw that in the movie too.
What was the title?
What's in your mouth?
A candy.
A candy kiss.
I hate candy.
You think we can even kiss?
My eyes.
Deul Rae!
Hey!
Wait for me.
Are you shy?
I can't believe this.
What?
- What kind of kiss is this?
- Hey.
What kind of kiss is this?
It's a park kiss that you
do in front of many people.
I thought you cared about
the concept of the kiss.
I asked you that to make you happy, honey.
Aren't you happy?
What I saw wasn't everything.
Oops.
Whatever.
What are you doing?
Are you sick?
My body noticed first that you're
coming because I wanted to throw up.
I got some drinks from the wedding company.
Don't talk to me as if nothing has happened.
This is my sacred workplace.
I don't want to talk about
some dirty, filthy stuff.
Why are you sitting there? Don't you
know I want you to get out here?
Nothing happened. That's why I'm
talking to you as if nothing happened.
Then what was it that I saw?
You imagined dirty and filthy things like that
because you love third-rated drama so much.
Reality is dirtier
and filthier than drama.
I realized it from you guys. I've felt
unpleasant about you and him being together.
I just didn't tell you. How can
a man and a woman be friends?
If so, one of you is probably hiding feelings
for the other just like you and Ki Joong.
You're trying to teach me again.
What you think is right, what you do
is right, and I have to follow that?
I tell you everything. I thought this
is how I express my trust for you.
Your feelings were like a trash can for me.
There were many times that I
didn't want to know how you felt.
I liked you a lot so I wanted to share all that I
could with you. But it was a burden to you.
I told you I didn't get much love from my parents when I grew up.
If somebody tells me she likes me, I
get so scared and start doubting.
Because I don't deserve to be loved.
And then you two became my friends.
You guys are the most important
people in my life.
There should be only one when
you use a word 'the most'.
Even now you're grouping me
and Jung Hoon as one person.
Anyways, Jung Hoon comes first before me.
What is it that you really want to know?
How are you related with
Shin Gang company in Busan?
Why were you with the CEO's son
at his funeral?
He was my brother.
Let's just stop talking about this.
You're the leading character and
I'm just your supporting actress.
The world revolves around you and
you only care about your problem.
Do you know what you said first
when you called me last night?
It was, 'you told Jung Hoon that
you're leaving before you left'.
It wasn't, 'are you okay?' or
'I was so worried about you'.
Because you're the leading role and you
only care about how you feel first.
I'm not going to stop you even
if you're breaking up with him.
I don't think it's because of me.
If you think I was your friend, don't take that blame on me at least.
The most active and fun
wind-up toy will be released.
What do you think?
I think you used that same sentence
when other toys were released.
No. It was my first time using it.
I like this one.
This will increase fine motor skills
and improve kids' concentration.
I want to have a wind up toy too.
I can't concentrate well recently.
See?
She fell for it.
Okay.
Then go with this.
- Who is this?
- Hey.
The caller is 'scary'?
Who is this?
Why did she come to my workplace?
Did Hae Yoon tell her we broke up?
I really hope she didn't do that yet.
She has a baby.
The game is over now.
I'm going to convince him.
- Mrs. Jung.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- I haven't bought you dinner yet.
I came to buy you dinner tonight.
Pick anywhere you want to eat.
- How can I help you?
- Give me a pregnancy test.
Here it is.
Where should I go?
Just tell me what you want to eat.
I'll buy you anything.
Do you like raw fish?
I do. But I'm not in the mood for that now.
Then would you like beef?
Well... I don't feel like eating beef.
Now I found what I want to eat.
I wish it was 6,500 won. It's too expensive.
The price hasn't been changed for years.
- It's not that expensive.
- But it's more expensive than the black noodle.
The answer was black noodle.
It's hot.
Be careful.
You too.
I've decided to trust you completely.
I heard you told your mom to pay
everything because we have more money.
- Yeah.
- I like it so much.
You should keep telling them that, okay?
Why aren't you answering?
Okay, Mrs. Jung.
Didn't you hear anything from Hae Yoon?
About the pregnancy? Do I have to pretend I don't know about it?
No, I didn't. Why? Did something happen?
Should I tell her we broke up?
What's that look on his face? He didn't want her to get pregnant?
Actually, Hae Yoon and I...
When are you going to print
wedding invitations?
What did she say about this?
Why do you ask what she thinks? Just
do what you want. Do it like a man.
Focus on the wedding from now on.
Eat like a man.
What's this?
The test says I'm not pregnant.
What's wrong with me?
It's making me crazy.
Let's get inside. Hae Yoon is home.
It's okay. I saw her this morning.
It's better if you see her one more time.
I know but I have to go home.
Sure. If that's the case, you should go.
Go then.
Bye.
Something's weird.
Did you tell Jung Hoon that you're pregnant?
- Who said I am?
- Are you not pregnant?
- Then why...
- I had a gastritis before.
Are you sure?
Did you take a pregnancy test?
- You know a lot of stuff.
- I'll go buy one then.
I did!
Do you want me to show you?
- Then what was wrong with him?
- Him who?
Jung Hoon. We had dinner together.
Why did you have dinner with him? You do
things that I don't even ask you to do.
Why do I have to do stuff
that you ask me to do?
Is it done already?
I just had to microwave them a little.
Looks delicious.
Jung Hoon still isn't home.
Honey, say something when he comes.
He should sleep in one place.
He's young.
You're a very understanding person.
- I'm home.
- Hey, come and sit here.
- Hi.
- Who were you with?
Are you going to keep sleeping out like this?
I was with Dong Bi.
You're so weird. Why do
you sleep in her house?
Can I not sleep at my friend's house?
I was so drunk so I slept there.
But your friend is a woman.
Honey, isn't this weird?
Besides, he was drunk.
- Why do people think it's weird?
- It looks weird.
- Does Hae Yoon know about this?
- Does she know?
The standard for this to be nothing is
if you aren't shameful to see
Hae Yoon.
- It's nothing.
- I'm glad to hear that.
By the way, why hasn't she contacted me yet?
She probably heard about the house.
She doesn't contact me first.
You should stop complaining now.
We decided to give up and accept them.
- I know but I get so mad.
- Let's just suck it up.
- We even help people we don't even know.
- I'd rather help them more.
You should ask her how she wants to
decorate the house. It's her house too.
I don't want to call her first.
It's not like you're dating her. It
sounds like you're playing hard to get.
You played hard to get when
you were dating me, didn't you?
Of course, I did. So I could make you love me more.
- Let's go to our room now.
- Sure.
What are you doing here?
Can we postpone the interior for the house?
Why? Your wedding is coming soon.
We should get an estimation first
but it might take a month.
Do you want to live on the street?
We can move here then.
No way. We're going to leave
after we get you married.
Understand her. We have
things to do now but
since you're interrupting us, she's getting mad.
Honey, what you said will make
him imagine a lot of things.
Oh my God. I'll just leave the room.
This can be a good thing because I was
worried about how I can forget about you.
Now everything is over.
Why was I naked?
What makes you so sure that
nothing happened between us?
I feel hot.
Let me take off your clothes.
Hae Yoon.
You're so mean.
Dong Bi.
Deul Rae, did something happen?
I wish everybody can be blessed.
What's wrong with you? Do you want
some water so you can calm down?
No. I want to keep this feeling.
What happened?
I can't show how I feel at my house.
My sister is watching me like a wildcat.
Hae Jin is preparing the
trial for her divorce.
And Hae Yoon has been
in a bad mood for days.
I shouldn't feel happy at the house.
Excuse me.
Dr. Nam isn't here now.
He has a night surgery tonight.
He changed schedules with Dr. Yoon.
He's heading to his house.
You don't have to tell me things like that.
She thinks she has become his wife now.
I'm at the hospital. I thought you were here.
I'm on the way to my house.
You said you'd stay at your friend's house.
The plan has changed.
- When are you going to come?
- I don't know yet.
Come to think of it, I have
some good evidence for you.
What is it?
I'll tell you when you come.
Daddy!
- Did you take a shower?
- No.
- Then let's take a shower together.
- I take a shower with Mom though.
Mom is a woman. It's fun to
take a shower with a man.
Okay!
- What are you doing here?
- I'm not leaving. Why do I have to leave?
I shouldn't have left in the first place.
What are you doing? You're
making our kid confused.
Maybe it's you who is confused. If you
don't want to live with me, then you leave.
Open your eyes. Good job!
Let me wash your hair.
That was scary.
I think they're planning
something just like you said.
My husband came back.
Have you been stressed lately?
I was stressed for my wedding.
I think that caused this. You need to get
rid of your stress as often as possible.
Don't bear it.
- How about a drink?
- It's a good way to get rid of stress.
You do have a conscience.
I've been waiting for you to call me.
Why did you do that?
You could've called me first.
Because I wasn't going to talk to you.
I felt like a loser.
Fine. Everybody is leaving me.
One more shot.
You drink fast. I'm not done making it.
Drink this first.
No. That's not strong.
You got esophagitis though.
I took the medicine. I'm prepared to drink.
I know you're good at preparing stuff.
One more.
Stop drinking.
Give me more please.
Are you trying to flirt with me?
Please give me more.
What do you want?
I feel weird.
- Please.
- Okay. I'll give you more.
Sang Jin.
- I don't have it.
- Okay. I'll give you more. Wait.
My feeling was a trash can?
She's a bitch.
What did I do wrong?
I told her everything about me. Is it
wrong to ask her to understand me?
It is wrong. Why do you tell her everything?
It just makes her tired.
It was wrong.
So I was wrong.
Are you crying?
No. I'm not crying.
I didn't cry either when I
broke up with Jung Hoon.
I did a good job, didn't I?
Stop drinking, Hae Yoon.
You drank too much. Stop.
- Why did you drink too much?
- No, I didn't.
Let's go home.
Wait.
Watch out for your head.
No, no. Wait.
What good timing.
It's this way.
Why does she get heavy if she drinks?
- So she can put you through suffering.
- I was joking.
- Drink some.
- But it's coffee, isn't it?
Don't you drink coffee?
I don't drink coffee on an empty stomach.
Why is your stomach empty?
Do you want some ramen?
I don't eat ramen. I have a sick stomach.
Then let me make some food.
Wait for a minute.
It's okay. I'll just eat at my house.
It's okay. Your wife wouldn't like it if
you tell her to make food at this time.
My wife isn't like that. She's very beautiful, nice and she respects me so much.
- I see.
- That was my dream wife.
- What?
- I'm not married yet.
Hae Yoon said you are.
- Did you get a divorce?
- Of course, I didn't.
I know it's hard to believe a handsome
man like me hasn't gotten married yet.
So you are not married.
- Do I look that old?
- You don't look young.
I knew it but it's kind of sad to hear that from you.
It's not good if a man looks young.
Looks so easy to others.
A lawyer should give people trust.
You're right. Making money
is important to live a life.
You're right.
Anyway, why is the trial going so slow?
I heard she will be investigated or something.
Not just once, but a couple times.
- And then, the mediation...
Yeah, that's how it goes. In order to get a
trial, you should go through a mediation step.
And before the mediation, you get investigated.
Things will end during the
mediation step usually.
It usually takes six months.
It's not going slow.
I see.
- I should get going now.
- Okay.
- You don't have to see me out.
- You're a big help to our family.
Please come often. I'll make you delicious food.
Alright.
Bye.
If I knew he was single, you thought
I was going to hook you up with him?
You think me as a bad mom. Do you think I'd
really do that when your wedding day was set?
Unless you break up with Jung Hoon.
Honey, I'm going to go to Jung Hoon's marital
house with Hae Yoon. You should come.
Did you tell her?
Not yet. I can tell
Jung Hoon to bring her.
- She'll be home. It's Saturday.
- Okay. I'll come home early.
- Have a good day, honey.
- Okay. You don't have to see me out.
But I want to.
I told you how happy I am
to live with you, didn't I?
No, you didn't.
That's not possible.
I forget things like that so easily.
I'm very happy to live with you.
Me too. I'm very happy to live with you too.
Have a great day.
I made some hang over soup.
Get up and have some.
Wake up and have some soup.
Mrs. Ha.
Hi, Mrs. Ha.
Are you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
You are. You don't call me anymore because I yelled at you last time.
I was going to ask Jung Hoon to bring
you here but I decided to do it.
Thank you, Mrs. Ha.
You heard about the house from your mom, right?
You should take a look too.
Why are you not saying anything?
Are you still mad at me?
No, I'm not.
I should take a look.
Then I'll see you at the apartment.
I'll text you the address.
Hi. I got a call from your mother.
You didn't tell her that we broke up.
She told me to come take a look at the marital home. I couldn't say no to that.
I don't want you to come.
Mr. Min would like to see you. He might sign the contract if he likes it.
Come in.
I'm Gong Ki Joong.
You look better than the picture.
You're having a meal now.Am I bothering you?
I didn't know you were eating since it isn't meal time now.
It's okay. I eat whenever I want to. Have a seat.
Have you looked at my project proposal?
It's not me who will make the decision.
Then why did you want to see me?
My daughter will do it. If she says yes, I will. But if she says no, I won't.
I guess she's here.
How dare you sit like that before I tell you to!
Look it over and tell me if you're going to do it or not.
This will be you first mission that I assign you.
You guys can talk about that.
You're still unilateral and self-righteous. You haven't changed a bit.
A man shouldn't be changed easily.
Brother Jeong Do just passed away. How could you do that?
You and I have a different way to forget about him.
I can't do this.
It's not in my hands anymore. You tell him that you won't do it.
You got dumped by him, didn't you?
It's a good chance to pay him back.
You really haven't changed a bit. You still use people's weaknesses to control them.
- That's how I win.
- You said a woman isn't human.
I'm still a woman.
Don't flatter yourself. You haven't passed yet.
You wanted to know about my family, right? He's my father.
- He's so scary.
- He thinks he lives in the Joseon dynasty.
He thinks he's the King.
So does my father. Every head of a rich family thinks like that.
They fight with their own family. If you lose the battle, then you're done.
So you do things you don't want to do to not lose the battle?
Even if it's a marriage of convenience?
In order to do what I want to do, I have to do what I don't want to do.
So, let's talk about us now.
Hearing 'us' from you, I guess you want to get invested from my father.
Do you think I'm that kind of person?
Then what is it?
I thought you had that much trust for each other.
There's nothing between us.
Because my love for you is finished.
Do you remember you told me I can always come back to you even if I think it's too late?
- I do.
- I guess that's not true anymore.
Since the love ended.
You still change your mind so easily. I guess we should talk about this when you calm down.
Why do you feel so confident about me?
You don't believe that I don't love you anymore, do you?
I don't believe that.
How can you not love me?
Because I love somebody else.
I told you not to come.
I didn't want to come.
What are you doing?
- Come in.
- Okay, Mrs. Ha.
- Hae Yoon. You're the last person that came.
- Hi, Mr. Ha.
You got prettier. Did you lose weight?
She's on a diet to wear a wedding dress.
No, I'm not.
What are you doing? Take a look with her and talk about how you guys want to decorate.
- Hae Yoon, we will follow your opinion.
- Thank you.
This is a bedroom.
Let's go.
- Why do they use the honorific?
- I think they're copying us.
Why didn't you tell them we broke up?
Why do you talk roughly all of a sudden? Use the honorific.
We broke up now. When are you going to tell them?
I'm thinking. They are all involved in our relationship now.
I can't tell them about this so easily.
And now we're in a place we could've lived together.
We might get married if you don't tell them soon.
Isn't that what you want? If you told your mom, this all will be over in a second.
Your mom had so many complaints while preparing the wedding.
She must be so happy to hear that.
Why did you lock the door? What were you two doing?
- It's nothing.
- So what do you think?
Mr. and Mrs. Ha, I'm sorry.
I can't keep lying to you guys.
We broke up.
- What?
- What do you mean? Break up?
- Mom, it's...
- You don't talk.
Hae Yoon, tell me.
- It's as what I said.
- When?
Why is that important?
It is to me. You guys broke up after I yelled at you, didn't you?
You guys had a fight over because of me and that led to the break up, right?
No, it's not because of you.
Since I'm not good enough for him, I gave up.
It's over. Don't try to make it better.
I tried to follow what you want because I wanted to win your favor.
But I never tried to make better something I can't.
Then did you guys both agree to break up or did you break up with him?
He accepted it.
That means you broke up with him, doesn't it?
Okay. Since we just heard about it, we need some time for ourselves.
I think we should stop it here.
Mr. Ha, thank you for everything you've done for me.
I really wanted to be a part of your family.
What's going on?
It's all my fault.
Why? Did she find out that you slept at Dong Bi's house?
Did she?
You said it's nothing.
It might be nothing for him but it isn't nothing for her.
Hae Yoon broke up with him first. Then this should be it.
It's so embarrassing.
Why do you think whatever you want to?
Then what is it? What's the reason she broke up with you? Is it because of me?
- No.
- Please make sure it's not because of me.
I don't want to be parents who ruin our child's wedding.
Do you only care about your dignity in this situation?
That's not what she means.
You two are panicking now.
What should I do? What should I tell my sister?
And what should I tell my friends about this?
How we are going tell others isn't important now.
We need to figure out how and why they broke up and then work it out.
What are you talking about? They broke up.
All we have left is to make it official to others.
I don't like what you said.
It's about how he and Hae Yoon feel about it.
Don't do things in a businesslike manner.
I didn't like this marriage from the beginning.
You should've ended it when we had the meeting with her parents.
If it has to end like this, then so be it.
Mom, I'm very disappointed.
Who do you think that suffers the most in this situation?
Is it you?
Where are you going?
Long time no see.
I know. Even if we see each other everyday, you always show me a new face.
Now you understand me better even if I twist words.
Maybe we should get married not divorced.
Sorry, I can't take that kind of joke yet.
I'm glad you think it's a joke. Please send your mom away. It's not fair.
Mind your own business.